<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on Ron Huang</title>
    <link>https://ron.hng.tw/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on Ron Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-TW</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ron.hng.tw/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>久違的中秋烤肉</title>
      <link>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/08/31/midautumn-bbq-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/08/31/midautumn-bbq-2011/</guid>
      <description>睽違三年的中秋烤肉又要回來了，照慣例要邀請小寶的同事來烤肉。跟往年一樣， 歡迎攜帶女伴一起參加唷。男伴就不用勉強了。 今年仍然有一個新的網站供各</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Calennar</title>
      <link>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/05/08/introducing-calennar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/05/08/introducing-calennar/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Calennar, seminar schedules in iCalendar format. Currently, this only support seminars from NUS School of Computing. You can subscribe Calennar into your favorite calendar client with the following URL:
http://inmate.ronhuang.org/calennar/nuscs.ics  NUS SoC offers many seminars. However, since I am not from SoC, I do not receive automatic email notifications for these seminars and often missed interesting ones. They do offer web for the seminar schedules, but there are no corresponding RSS or Twitter account to subscribe to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embed Tweet with a Single Line of Code</title>
      <link>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/04/04/embed-tweet-with-a-single-line-of-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/04/04/embed-tweet-with-a-single-line-of-code/</guid>
      <description>Updated in 2015/12/28: this widget is no longer usable. Please refer to Embed a Single Tweet for similar feature.
In my previous post, I needed to show a tweet. Though I could have embedded a picture of the tweet, I would really prefer a functional one, where the links, mentions, and hashtags are all linkified. But I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to find any useful ones beside Blackbird Pie. Blackbird Pie was OK, but it requires users to manually generate the tweet and embed the generated HTML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Friendly Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/03/28/taiwan-friendly-wikipedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ron.hng.tw/2011/03/28/taiwan-friendly-wikipedia/</guid>
      <description>Although Wikipedia provides menu to switch from different Chinese variants, Wikipedia doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to remember to the users&amp;rsquo; selection. I am tired of manually going through the menu and selecting Traditional Chinese (Taiwan) whenever I browse a new Wikipedia article. So I created Taiwan Friendly Wikipedia, a Google Chrome extension to automatically redirect to the Traditional Chinese (Taiwan) variant when reading Chinese articles.
Users can switch off the automatic redirection in the options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter user names with less than two characters</title>
      <link>https://ron.hng.tw/2010/07/22/twitter-user-names-with-less-than-two-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ron.hng.tw/2010/07/22/twitter-user-names-with-less-than-two-characters/</guid>
      <description>Updated in 2012/12/02: moved table to Google Docs.
Today I was curious if all the Twitter user names with less than two characters are already created. So I wrote a tiny script to check.
The result is: YES! All of them are already created. In fact, the last one, lh, was just created today! What a coincidence. However, quite a few user names are suspended, and user name me also seems to be reserved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>